{
    "id": "pehu",
    "name": "Pehu",
    "yomi": "ペフ",
    "text": [
        "わたしたちは、あなたの素晴らしいアイデアや創造的なチャレンジをサポートします。",
        "We Support Your Amazing Ideas and Creative Challenges"
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Website",
            "href": "https://pehu.creative-community.space/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Something",
            "jp": "何か",
            "yes": "to listen",
            "left": "聞く",
            "no": "to hear",
            "right": "聞こえる"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "I",
            "jp": "何かを",
            "yes": "look all",
            "left": "見る",
            "no": "see all",
            "right": "眺める"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "If there are a lot you'd",
            "jp": "たくさんあったら",
            "yes": "choose one",
            "left": "選ぶ",
            "no": "choose nothing",
            "right": "選ばない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Breath",
            "jp": "息を",
            "yes": "in and out",
            "left": "する",
            "no": "stop",
            "right": "止める"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "Eyes",
            "jp": "目を",
            "yes": "closed tight",
            "left": "閉じる",
            "no": "wide shut",
            "right": "瞑る"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Your surrounding there is",
            "jp": "周りに",
            "yes": "something",
            "left": "何かある",
            "no": "nothing",
            "right": "何もない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Peeling off means",
            "jp": "はがれてる",
            "yes": "zero",
            "left": "ゼロ",
            "no": "minus",
            "right": "マイナス"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Air",
            "jp": "空気",
            "yes": "want some",
            "left": "ほしい",
            "no": "it&#039;s filled",
            "right": "いっぱい"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Something",
            "jp": "何か",
            "yes": "to touch",
            "left": "触る",
            "no": "to feel",
            "right": "触れる"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Does it last all the way?",
            "jp": "ずっと続いてる？",
            "yes": "yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "no",
            "right": "いいえ"
        }
    ]
}